A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Administrative Files, RG 1 FA427
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administrative, 1952, 1954-2006; 1; 108.25 Cubic Feet 246 document boxes.
  - ACC records, 1955-1958, 1960-2006; 2
    - Program Files, 1978, 1980-1996; 4
      - Miscellaneous, 1986-1994; 4
        - "A Collector's Eye", in India, 1989 December-1990 April (Box 131, Folder 3850)
        - American Dance Festival, 1989 June, 1987-1990 (Box 131, Folder 3851)
        - American Dance Festival, Birju Maharaj Khatak Group, 1990-1991 (Box 131, Folder 3852)
        - Archaeology, Low-Altitude Aerial Photography Workshop, 1992 (Box 131, Folder 3853)
        - Blue Grass Band, Connel, Dudley, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 3854)
        - Chittick, William, Seminar on Sufism, Delhi, India, 1991 November 11-13 (Box 131, Folder 3855)
        - Craft Exchange, 1990, 1992 (Box 131, Folder 3856)
        - Dance Critics, 1990-1991 (Box 131, Folder 3857)
        - Desai, Vishakha, Director Asia Society Galleries, Exhibit: Gods, Guardians and Lovers, 1990-1991 (Box 131, Folder 3858)
        - Exchange of Musicians to India, 1992 January, 1990-1992 (Box 131, Folder 3859)
        - Exchange of Musicians to U. S., 1992 October, 1992-1993 (Box 131, Folder 3860)
        - Exchange of Writers, Kit Reed, 1990-1992 (Box 131, Folder 3861)
        - Exchanges in Field of Archaeology, 1986-1987 (Box 131, Folder 3862)
        - Indira Gandhi National Center for the Arts (IGNCA), Maurice Friedman, Lecturer, 1992 Janaury, 1990-1992 (Box 131, Folder 3863)
        - International Visitorship, S. Gopal, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 3864)
        - Joe Reed Exhibition, USIS (United States Information Service), Delhi, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 3865)
        - Jung, Anees, 1991 (Box 131, Folder 3866)
        - Kala, International Seminar on Time, Kapila Vatsyayan, Indira Gandhi National Center for the Arts, New Delhi, 1989-1991 (Box 131, Folder 3867)
        - Kala, International Seminar on Time, Kapila Vatsyayan, Indira Gandhi National Center for the Arts, New Delhi, 1989-1991 (Box 131, Folder 3867A)
        - Khare, Harish, USIF Travel Grant for Research in the U. S., 1992 May (Box 131, Folder 3868)
        - Laetsch, Mac, Advance Trip, Education Programs, 1991 (Box 131, Folder 3869)
        - Landry, Richard & Babs Case, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 3870)
        - Landry, Richard & Babs Case, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 3870A)
        - Law & Social Change Book, 1987 (Box 131, Folder 3871)
        - Mansingh, Sonal, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 3872)
        - Markel, Stephen, Museum Visit, 1989-1990 (Box 131, Folder 3873)
        - Merce Cunningham, 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 132, Folder 3874)
        - Merce Cunningham Company, Art Becofsky & Colmann Rupp Trip, 1990 (Box 132, Folder 3875)
        - National Dance Institute, Celebration of India Project, 1991 June, 1989-1992 (Box 132, Folder 3876)
        - National Dance Institute, "Event of the Year", Press Information, Manjushri Sircar, 1991 (Box 132, Folder 3877)
        - National Dance Institute, 2nd Visit to India, 1989 December-1990 January, 1989, 1992 (Box 132, Folder 3878)
        - National Dance Institute Film Project, Cancelled, 1990-1991 (Box 132, Folder 3879)
        - Nikolais/Murray Louis Dance Theater, 1989-1991, 1993 (Box 132, Folder 3880)
        - Par-Painting of Rahasthan, Video Project, Translator, 1990-1993 (Box 132, Folder 3881)
        - The Peaceful Conquerors, Jain Art, Pratapaditya Pal, Advanced Trip, 1991-1994 (Box 132, Folder 3882)
        - Pingree, David, Visitorship, 1991 (Box 132, Folder 3883)
        - Reinhart, Charles, 1989 November 25-December 4 (Box 132, Folder 3884)
        - Reinhart, Charles, American Dance Festival, 1990-1991 (Box 132, Folder 3885)
        - Restoration at Alchi Monastery, Ladakh, 1991-1993 (Box 132, Folder 3886)
        - Richards, Lloyd, Yale Repertory, 1990-1992 (Box 132, Folder 3887)
        - Roundtable on Contemporary Art, Asia Society, 1991-1992 (Box 132, Folder 3888)
        - Rudel, Julius, 1992 (Box 133, Folder 3889)
        - Sangeet Natak Theater Festival, New Delhi, September 3-17, 1989-1990 (Box 133, Folder 3890)
        - Seminar on Congressional Committee System, India, 1986 November 18-19, 1985-1986 (Box 133, Folder 3891)
        - Seminar on Radha Krishnan and Adi Sankara, 1989 February 14, 1988-1989 (Box 133, Folder 3892)
        - Sircar, Ranjabati, American Dance Festival/National Dance Institute, 1989-1990 (Box 133, Folder 3893)
        - Skinner, Richard, Museum Lighting, In India, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 3894)
        - USEFI (United States Educational Foundation in India), Education Program, 1991 (Box 133, Folder 3895)
        - Valli, Alarmel, Indian Dancer, 1988-1990 (Box 133, Folder 3896)
        - Visit of Purnima Shah, 1989 June-July (Box 133, Folder 3897)
        - Visit of Sonal Mansingh to U. S., 1990 August-September (Box 133, Folder 3898)
        - Writers Workshop, U. S. Program, 1992 October, 1991-1992 (Box 133, Folder 3899)
        - Yankee Traders and Calcutta Merchants, 1989-1991 (Box 133, Folder 3900)
      - Museum, 1982, 1986-1993; 5
        - Bierman, Irene, World Calligraphy Seminar and Exhibition, 1988 December 5-10 (Box 133, Folder 3901)
        - Chakravarty, Kalyan Kumar, Grantee to Harvard, 1991 (Box 133, Folder 3902)
        - Distinguished Visitor Program, Justice K. Jagannatha Shetty and Sunhash Chandra Birla, 1990 August (Box 133, Folder 3903)
        - Exchange of Museum Personnel, David Imbrogno, 1992-1993 (Box 133, Folder 3904)
        - Exchange of Museum Personnel, David Imbrogno, 1992-1993 (Box 133, Folder 3904A)
          Restricted from scholarly access- Confidential material
        - Exchange of Museum Personnel, Dilip Pathak, 1991-1993 (Box 133, Folder 3905)
        - Exchange with Prince of Wales Museum, Bombay, Savita A. Sarda, 1990 (Box 133, Folder 3906)
        - International Seminar on Visual Anthropology, In India, Rakhi Roy and Jayasinhji Jhala, 1986 (Box 133, Folder 3907)
        - Kumar, Ram, Visit, 1989 June-July, 1988-1989 (Box 133, Folder 3908)
        - Mirdha, Ram Niwas, Vistorship Program, 1990 (Box 133, Folder 3909)
        - Museum Exchange Program, Bartholomew, Terese, 1982, 1987-1988 (Box 133, Folder 3910)
        - Museum Exchange Program, Basu, Swati, Natural Museum of Natural History to U. S., 1991-1993 (Box 133, Folder 3911)
        - Museum Exchange Program, Bhaumik, P. K. and S. Rajgopal, 1987-1988 (Box 134, Folder 3912)
        - Museum Exchange Program, Desai, Vishakha, 1988-1989 (Box 134, Folder 3913)
        - Museum Exchange Program, Garg, K. L., 1989 May, 1988-1989 (Box 134, Folder 3914)
        - Museum Exchange Program, General, 1986-1988 (Box 134, Folder 3915)
        - Museum Exchange Program, Gutsch, William, to India, 1989 November, 1988-1989 (Box 134, Folder 3916)
        - Museum Exchange Program, Jain, Kamal, Getty Conservation Institute, 1991 February 25 (Box 134, Folder 3917)
        - Museum Exchange Program, Leoshko, Janice, 1987 November-December (Box 134, Folder 3918)
        - Museum Exchange Program, Mukherjee, Dolly, 1988-1989 (Box 134, Folder 3919)
        - Museum Exchange Program, Satyamurthy, T., 1988-1989 (Box 134, Folder 3920)
        - Museum Exchange Program, Shah, Nematullah, 1986-1988 (Box 134, Folder 3921)
        - Museum Exchange Program, Upadhyay, Ram Sahay, 1989 April (Box 134, Folder 3922)
        - Narmada River Dam, Conference, 1992 March 27-28, 1991-1992 (Box 134, Folder 3923)
        - Poster, Amy, Terra Cotta Project, 1988-1990 (Box 134, Folder 3924)
        - Poster, Amy and Lambertus Van Zelst, 1988 January, 1986-1988 (Box 134, Folder 3925)
        - Poster, Amy and Lambertus Van Zelst, 1988 January, 1986-1988 (Box 134, Folder 3925A)
        - Programs with Indira Gandhi Nation Centre for the Arts and New York Public Library, 1988-1989 (Box 134, Folder 3926)
        - Sheikh, Gulam, Artist-in-Residence, Art Institute of Chicago, 1987 September (Box 134, Folder 3927)
        - Vatsysyan, Kapila, Indira Gandhi National Centre for the Arts, 1990-1991 (Box 134, Folder 3928)
        - Visit of Rajeev Sethi to U. S., via Favrot Fund, 1989 November (Box 134, Folder 3929)
        - Weissbort, Daneil, Sahitya Akademi's Translation Conference, 1990 January 3, 1989 (Box 134, Folder 3930)
      - Natural History, 1980-1981, 1983, 1985-1986, 1990-1992; 6
        - Nair, S. M., Visit, 1990 November 25 (Box 134, Folder 3931)
        - Publications on Finding on Natural History Workshops (Folder 1 of 2), 1980-1981, 1983, 1985-1986, 1991-1992 (Box 134, Folder 3932)
        - Publications on Finding on Natural History Workshops (Folder 1 of 2), 1980-1981, 1983, 1985-1986, 1991-1992 (Box 135, Folder 3933)
        - VIII, Natural History Workshop, Architecture & Design for Natural History Museums, 1990 (Box 135, Folder 3934)
        - IX Natural History Workshop, Processes of Exhibit & Program Development, 1991 (Box 135, Folder 3935)
        - X Natural History Workshop, Environmentally Oriented Natural History Museum, 1992-1993 (Box 135, Folder 3936)
      - Science, 1984-1996; 7
        - Capsule Newsletter and Pamphlets, 1986-1995 (Box 135, Folder 3937)
        - Exhibitions, Association of Science-Technology Centers (ASTC), "Structures", 1986-1988, 1993 (Box 135, Folder 3938)
        - Exhibitions, "25 Years of Space Photography", 1986 November-1987 October, 1985-1989 (Box 135, Folder 3939)
        - Exhibitions, "25 Years of Space Photography", Stewart Andy Collins, 1986 November-December, 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 3940)
        - Exhibitions, "25 Years of Space Photography", Ellis Miner, 1987 May, 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 3941)
        - Exhibitions, "25 Years of Space Photography", Jay Belloli & Jurrie van der Woude, 1986 November-December, 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 3942)
        - Exhibitions, "25 Years of Space Photography", Jay Belloli & Jurrie van der Woude, 1987 October (Box 135, Folder 3943)
        - Exhibitions, "25 Years of Space Photography", R. Stephen Saunders, 1987 March (Box 135, Folder 3944)
        - Exhibitions, "25 Years of Space Photography", Science Lecturers, General Information, 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 3945)
        - Exhibitions, "25 Years of Space Photography", Stephen D. Wall, 1987 October (Box 135, Folder 3946)
        - Exhibitions, "25 Years of Space Photography", William McLaughlin, 1987 July, 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 3947)
        - Finn, Bernard, National Museum of American History, "Information Revolution" Exhibition, Travel to India, 1988 January 14, 1986-1988 (Box 135, Folder 3948)
        - Ghose, Saroj, Science & Technology Exhibit, 1984, 1986-1989 (Box 135, Folder 3949)
        - Information and Communication, A New Approach to Science Museums, India, 1990 December, 1990-1991 (Box 135, Folder 3950)
        - "Interactive Video Tech" Workshop, Panelist Invites, Information Letters, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 3951)
        - Learning Technologies, Inc., Starlab Projection Bulbs, 1996 (Box 136, Folder 3952)
        - National Council of Science Museums, Saroj Ghose, 1984-1988 (Box 136, Folder 3953)
        - National Council of Science Museums, Saroj Ghose, 1988-1995 (Box 136, Folder 3954)
        - "Use of High Technology in Science Museums", Boston, 1987 September 28-29, 1987-1988 (Box 136, Folder 3955)
        - Water Workshop, Los Angeles, 1992 February 10-15, 1992-1993 (Box 136, Folder 3956)
        - Workshop, "Development of Exhibitions on Chemistry in Science Centers", 1989 October, 1989-1990 (Box 136, Folder 3957)
        - Workshop, "Ellipses in Nature and in the Mind", in India, 1988 April-May (Box 136, Folder 3958)
        - Workshop, "Museum Without Walls", in India, 1988 December, 1987-1989 (Box 136, Folder 3959)
      - Sports Exchange, 1986-1996; 8
        - Atchison, David, Golf, 1992 August (Box 136, Folder 3960)
        - Bartsch, Ed, Swimming Coach, 1990 August 3-31 (Box 136, Folder 3961)
        - Body, David, Architect, 1990 September 1-10 (Box 137, Folder 3962)
        - Budget (Box 137, Folder 3963)
        - Bullard, Ernie, Track and Field Coach, 1988 July 16-August 4, 1987-1989 (Box 137, Folder 3964)
        - Callaghan, John, Bio & Doctor's Letter, 1988-1989 (Box 137, Folder 3965)
        - Callaghan, John, Visit, 1986 October, 1986-1987 (Box 137, Folder 3966)
        - Callaghan, John, Visit, 1987 August 9-20 (Box 137, Folder 3967)
        - Callaghan, John and John Hubbard, India, 1993 May 9-21 (Box 137, Folder 3968)
        - Callaghan, John and John Hubbard, India, 1993 May 9-21 (Box 137, Folder 3968A)
        - Canceled Sports Specialists, 1988, 1990, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 3969)
        - Contarsy, Steve, Assistant Swim Coach, 1990 August 15-31 (Box 137, Folder 3970)
        - Dey, Rabindra Nath, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 3971)
        - Dey, Swadan Kumar & P. Majumdar, Indian Physiologists, University of Southern California, 1994 September (Box 137, Folder 3972)
        - Exchange of Coaches, General Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 137, Folder 3973)
        - Frost, John, Tennis, 1990 June 26-July 30, 1990-1991 (Box 137, Folder 3974)
        - General Correspondence, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 3975)
        - General Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 137, Folder 3976)
        - General Correspondence, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 3977)
        - General Correspondence, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 3978)
        - Girandola, Robert, Physiologist, 1990 July 14-August 1, 1990-1991 (Box 137, Folder 3979)
        - Girandola, Robert, Nutritionist, 1992 August (Box 138, Folder 3980)
        - Girandola, Robert, Nutritionist, 1992 August (Box 138, Folder 3980A)
        - Golf Architect, 1993 (Box 138, Folder 3981)
        - Hubbard, John R., Correspondence, 1995 (Box 138, Folder 3982)
        - Indian Basketball Team to the U.S., 1992 November 10-24, 1992-1993 (Box 138, Folder 3983)
        - Indian Coaches to U.S. Colleges, 1992-1993 (Box 138, Folder 3984)
        - Keifer, James, Track & Field, 1990 July 12-August 3 (Box 138, Folder 3985)
        - Lien, Randy, Golf, 1990 August 1-19 (Box 138, Folder 3986)
        - McLean, Douglas J., Yachting Coach, 1990 July 3-20 (Box 138, Folder 3987)
        - Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 138, Folder 3988)
        - Morrison, Stanley, Basketball, 1990 June 1-15 (Box 138, Folder 3989)
        - O'Connor, Robert, Weight Training, 1992 August (Box 138, Folder 3990)
        - O'Connor, Robert, Weight Training, 1992 August (Box 138, Folder 3990A)
        - Osness, Wayne, Exercise Physiologist, 1992 August (Box 138, Folder 3991)
        - Osness, Wayne, 1993 May 19-June 1 (Box 138, Folder 3992)
        - Osness, Wayne, 1993 May 19-June 1 (Box 138, Folder 3992A)
        - Osness, Wayne, 1996 January, 1995-1996 (Box 138, Folder 3993)
        - Ryska, Tod, Tennis, 1992 August (Box 138, Folder 3994)
        - Ryska, Tod, Tennis, 1992 August (Box 138, Folder 3994A)
        - Simons, Jeffery, Psychologist, 1991 January 15-February 4, 1990-1992 (Box 138, Folder 3995)
        - Simons, Jeffery, Pyschologist, 1992 December 29-1993 January 12, 1991-1993 (Box 138, Folder 3996)
        - Singh, Jajendra, Sports Psychologist, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 3997)
        - Varma, Arvin, Graduate Student, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 3998)
        - Varma, Arvin, Graduate Student, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 3998A)
          Restricted form scholarly access-Confidential material
        - Visit of Psychologist, Biochemist & Physiologist, 1988-1989 (Box 138, Folder 3999)
        - Wiswell, Robert, Drug Control, 1990 July 14-28 (Box 139, Folder 4000)
        - Wiswell, Robert, Drug Control, 1990 July 14-28 (Box 139, Folder 4000A)
        - Workshop on Athletics, "Sports Management", 1988-1989 (Box 139, Folder 4001)
        - Workshop on Athletics, "Sports Management", 1988-1989 (Box 139, Folder 4001A)
    - Director's Office, 1955-1958, 1960-1998; 5
      Subseries 1: Asian Educational Institutions Subseries 2: Asian Foundations Subseries 3: Asian Individuals Subseries 4: Asian Museums Subseries 5: Asian Organizations Subseries 6: International Agencies Subseries 7: Other Organizations Subseries 8: U. S. Educational Institutions Subseries 9: U. S. Foundations Subseries 10: U. S. Individuals Subseries 11: U. S. Museums Subseries 12: U. S. Organizations
      - Asian Educational Institutions, 1966, 1968-1969, 1971-1975, 1977-1985, 1988, 1990; 1
        - Bangladesh, 1972-1975, 1977 (Box 139, Folder 4002)
        - Hong Kong, 1968-1969, 1980, 1982, 1988 (Box 138, Folder 4003)
        - Institute of Asian Studies, 1984 (Box 139, Folder 4004)
        - The Kuppuswami Sastri Research Institute, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 4005)
        - Lalit Kala Akademi, 1966, 1971, 1979, 1981-1985 (Box 139, Folder 4006)
        - National Taiwan University, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 4007)
        - Takasaki College of Music, 1978, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 4008)
        - Thammasat University, 1982-1983, 1988 (Box 139, Folder 4009)
        - University of the Philippines, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 4010)
      - Asian Foundations, 1978-1988; 2
        - Japan, General, 1978, 1982, 1984, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 4011)
        - Korea, Daewoo Foundation, 1981-1986, 1988 (Box 139, Folder 4012)
        - Korea, General, 1979-1982, 1984-1985, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 4013)
      - Asian Individuals, 1955-1958, 1961, 1963-1996, 1998; 3
        - A, 1966-1967, 1970-1971, 1973-1976, 1978-1994
          - Ab-Ag, 1979-1982, 1985-1986, 1990-1994 (Box 139, Folder 4014)
          - Agashe, Mohan, 1980-1981, 1985, 1988 (Box 139, Folder 4015)
          - Ah-Ak, 1973, 1979-1991 (Box 140, Folder 4016)
          - Ah-Ak, 1973, 1979-1991 (Box 140, Folder 4016)
          - Al, 1976, 1980-1981, 1985-1988, 1990-1993 (Box 140, Folder 4017)
          - Alam, Kurshia, 1983, 1985-1988 (Box 140, Folder 4018)
          - Am-An, 1975, 1979-1980, 1983-1984, 1986-1994 (Box 140, Folder 4019)
          - Ao, 1978-1984, 1988, 1992 (Box 140, Folder 4020)
          - Ao, 1978-1984, 1988, 1992 (Box 140, Folder 4020A)
          - Aoki, Yoichi, 1966-1967, 1970-1971, 1983-1984, 1986-1990 (Box 140, Folder 4021)
          - Aquino, Rogelio, 1982, 1984-1985, 1988-1989 (Box 141, Folder 4022)
          - Ar, 1974, 1979-1983, 1986-1992 (Box 141, Folder 4023)
          - Armentrout, Fred, 1980-1985 (Box 141, Folder 4024)
          - As-At, 1981, 1983, 1985, 1987-1990 (Box 141, Folder 4025)
          - As-At, 1981, 1983, 1985, 1987-1990 (Box 141, Folder 4025A)
          - Aw-Az, 1980-1986, 1989-1991 (Box 141, Folder 4026)
        - B, 1969-1977, 1979-1994
          - Bab-Bal, 1969, 1977, 1979-1980, 1982, 1986-1993 (Box 141, Folder 4027)
          - Bab-Bal, 1969, 1977, 1979-1980, 1982, 1986-1993 (Box 141, Folder 4027A)
          - Ban-Bap, 1980, 1983-1986, 1991-1993 (Box 142, Folder 4028)
          - Bar-Bax, 1969-1975, 1981-1984, 1986, 1988-1990 (Box 142, Folder 4029)
          - Bhagat-Bhattacharyya, 1970-1971, 1975-1976, 1980-1983, 1987-1992 (Box 142, Folder 4030)
          - Bhattarai-Byun, 1977, 1979-1992, 1994 (Box 142, Folder 4031)
          - Bhattarai-Byun, 1977, 1979-1992, 1994 (Box 142, Folder 4031A)
        - C, 1967, 1971, 1973-1994
          - Ca-Chak, 1984-1992 (Box 142, Folder 4032)
          - Ca-Chak, 1984-1992 (Box 142, Folder 4032A)
          - Ca-Chak, 1984-1992 (Box 248, Folder 4719)
          - Chan-Chand, 1967, 1977, 1979-1981, 1983-1988, 1990 (Box 143, Folder 4033)
          - Chan-Chand, 1967, 1977, 1979-1981, 1983-1988, 1990 (Box 143, Folder 4033A)
          - Chang-Chau, 1978-1981, 1984-1994 (Box 143, Folder 4034)
          - Chang-Chau, 1978-1981, 1984-1994 (Box 143, Folder 4034A)
          - Chatterjee, Khitish, 1984-1989 (Box 143, Folder 4035)
          - Chen, Cecelia-Chen, Long-Bin, 1981-1982, 1984-1985, 1987-1994 (Box 143, Folder 4036)
          - Chen, Cecilia-Chen, Long-Bin, 1981-1982, 1984-1985, 1987-1994 (Box 143, Folder 4036A)
          - Chen, Miaping-Chen, Xian Yuan, 1985-1994 (Box 143, Folder 4037)
          - Chen, Maiping-Chen, Xian Yuan, 1985-1994 (Box 143, Folder 4037A)
          - Chen, Yi-Chen, Zhongqiu, 1985-1991 (Box 144, Folder 4038)
          - Chen, Yi-Chen, Zhongqiu, 1985-1991 (Box 144, Folder 4038A)
          - Chen, Yi-Fei, 1983, 1988, 1990 (Box 144, Folder 4039)
          - Chen, Yi-Fei, 1983, 1988, 1990 (Box 248, Folder 4720)
          - Cheng-Chiang, 1976-1977, 1979-1983, 1986-1994 (Box 144, Folder 4040)
          - Cheng-Chiang, 1976-1977, 1979-1983, 1986-1994 (Box 144, Folder 4040A)
          - Cheng-Chiang, 1976-1977, 1979-1983, 1986-1994 (Box 248, Folder 4721)
          - Chiao-Chou, She-Wei, 1981, 1983, 1985-1986, 1989-1991, 1993-1994 (Box 144, Folder 4041)
          - Chiao-Chou, She-Wei, 1981, 1983, 1985-1986, 1989-1991, 1993-1994 (Box 144, Folder 4041A)
            Restrictred from scholarly access-Confidential material
          - Choudhury-Chu, Tak Kwan, 1975, 1981-1982, 1985-1990, 1992, 1994 (Box 144, Folder 4042)
          - Choudhury-Chu, Tak Kwan, 1975, 1981-1982, 1985-1990, 1992, 1994 (Box 144, Folder 4042A)
          - Chua, Pastor L., Jr-Cu, 1971, 1973-1980, 1982-1984, 1986-1987, 1989-1991, 1993-1994 (Box 145, Folder 4043)
        - D, 1967, 1971, 1973-1994
          - Dab-Das Chauhan, Hari Govind, 1969, 1972, 1977, 1980-1990, 1992 (Box 145, Folder 4044)
          - Das Gupta, Aloke-Del, 1968-1970, 1974-1975, 1980-1982, 1984-1987, 1990-1994 (Box 145, Folder 4045)
          - Das Gupta, Aloke-Del, 1968-1970, 1974-1975, 1980-1982, 1984-1987, 1990-1994 (Box 145, Folder 4045A)
          - De, Arijit, 1983-1985 (Box 145, Folder 4046)
          - Den-Des, 1975-1976, 1978, 1980-1987, 1990-1991 (Box 145, Folder 4047)
          - Detha, Prakash, 1988-1991 (Box 146, Folder 4048)
          - Dev, 1981-1982, 1985-1987, 1989-1993 (Box 146, Folder 4049)
          - Dh-Di, 1969-1971, 1975-1980, 1984-1987, 1991-1992 (Box 146, Folder 4050)
          - Dhavalikar, M. K., 1965, 1971, 1973-1975 (Box 146, Folder 4051)
          - Do-Dw, 1980-1981, 1983, 1985, 1987-1992 (Box 146, Folder 4052)
        - E, 1971-1973, 1980-1983, 1985-1989 (Box 147, Folder 4053)
        - F, 1963-1967, 1980, 1982-1984, 1986-1994
          - Fa-Fr, 1979-1980, 1982, 1984-1992 (Box 147, Folder 4054)
          - Fa-Fr, 1979-1980, 1982, 1984-1992 (Box 147, Folder 4054A)
          - Fei, Dawai, 1989-1991 (Box 147, Folder 4055)
          - Florentino, Albertino, 1963-1967, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 4056)
          - Fu, Guoxi, 1990-1992 (Box 147, Folder 40457)
          - Fu, Guoxi, 1990-1992 (Box 147, Folder 4057A)
          - Fu, Jun-Fuijmura, Miyako, 1982-1984, 1986-1992 (Box 147, Folder 4058)
          - Fu, Jun-Fuijmura, Miyako, 1982-1984, 1986-1992 (Box 147, Folder 4058A)
          - Fu, Jun-Fujimura, Miyako, 1982-1984, 1986-1992 (Box 248, Folder 4722)
          - Fujino, Masayuki-Fur, 1980, 1982-1983, 1986-1989, 1991, 1993-1994 (Box 148, Folder 4059)
          - Fujino, Masayuki-Fur, 1980, 1982-1983, 1986-1989, 1991, 1993-1994 (Box 148, Folder 4059A)
          - Fujino, Masayuki-Fur, 1980, 1982-1983, 1986-1989, 1991-1993-1994 (Box 248, Folder 4723)
        - G, 1966-1969, 1971-1990, 1992-1994
          - Ga, 1966-1969, 1972, 1975, 1980-1990, 1992-1994 (Box 148, Folder 4060)
          - Ga, 1966-1969, 1972, 1975, 1980-1990, 1992-1994 (Box 148, Folder 4060A)
          - Ge-Gh, 1984-1985, 1987-1992 (Box 148, Folder 4061)
          - Ge-Gh, 1984-1985, 1987-1992 (Box 148, Folder 4061A)
          - Go-Gua, 1966, 1968, 1971, 1973, 1975, 1977, 1979-1983, 1985-1991 (Box 148, Folder 4062)
          - Goonetileke, H. A. Ian, 1975-1980, 1990 (Box 148, Folder 4063)
          - Guh-Gur, 1971, 1973-1974, 1976-1981, 1984-1991 (Box 149, Folder 4064)
          - Guh-Gur, 1971, 1973-1974, 1976-1981, 1984-1991 (Box 149, Folder 4064A)
            Restricted from scholarly access-Confidnetial material
          - Guo, Hu-Sheng, 1988-1989 (Box 149, Folder 4065)
          - Guo, Hu-Sheng, 1988-1989 (Box 149, Folder 4065A)
          - Gurung, Raju, 1983-1985, 1988-1990 (Box 149, Folder 4066)